propertynews.com 2001-06-29

# PropertyNews.com Online Privacy Policy

PropertyNews.com Online Privacy Policy **

PROPERTYNEWS.com LIMITED ("PropertyNews.com")

ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY

**

By accessing or using the PropertyNews.com Web site, you acknowledge and agree to the terms of the PropertyNews.com Online Privacy Policy, as outlined below. PropertyNews.com reserves the right to change its Online Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Any policy changes, either for company reasons or due to future legislation, will be posted on this page. Your use of this site will be subject to the version of PropertyNews.com Online Privacy Policy current at the time of such use.

PropertyNews.com is committed to protecting the privacy of its users. We want to provide a safe, secure user experience. We collect from you only sufficient personal data to enable us to provide you with the service or services you have requested. This data consists solely of information which you supply to us. Except as provided in this privacy policy, we do not supply your personal data to any other person unless you have expressly authorised us to do so.

**

Safeguarding of Data

**

Your personal information is kept as secure as possible through the use of technology and protection systems which are designed to keep your personal data secure. Access to your personal data is only provided to those employees necessary to help with the service(s) which we offer.

**

Registration

**

To register with PropertyNews.com you must provide your e-mail address and password. You may also choose to provide your address and other contact information. The information collected on the registration form is for several reasons including (i) to allow us to send messages to you when managing enquiries online (ii) to allow us to contact you for user service, if necessary; and (iii) to customise the content of our site to meet your specific needs.

**

Partners

**

PropertyNews.com has several necessary service partners who assist in providing the service(s) associated with the site. As part of the operations of the site, these companies may have access to your personal data. In addition we may partner with businesses to provide special services to our users. This type of use of personal data is called a "Secondary Use" because it is not necessary to the operation of the site. If PropertyNews.com proposes to make a Secondary Use of your personal data, the PropertyNews.com site will provide you with instructions on how to decline this service.

**

General Information

**

In general, we gather information about all of our users collectively, such as what areas users visit most frequently and what services users access the most. We only use such data in the aggregate. This information enables us to look at such matters as demographic and geographic trends and helps us determine what is most beneficial for our users, and how we can continually create a better overall user experience. We may share this information with our partners, but only in the aggregate, so that they too may understand how PropertyNews.com users, collectively, use our site.

**

Personal Information

**

In some instances, such as on the registration page, we may seek more specific information about you. This information may include your name, address, telephone number, postcode etc. With your permission, we may use that information to make you aware of additional products and services that you may find of interest, or to contact you regarding site updates and enhancements. We may also ask you for other information such as your interests, your likes and dislikes regarding the site, and lifestyle questions in an effort to deliver you the best possible site experience.

**

Opt Out

**

PropertyNews.com is set up so that after registration you may opt to receive subsequent deliveries of information, such as property alerts, notice of site upgrades and enhancements, new features, user tips, and additional information on products and services. Should you desire to remove your name from our database and "opt out" from receiving this information, please complete the relevant section of your personal profile.

**

Disclosure of Information

**

PropertyNews.com will not disclose information about your individual visits to our website or any of the personal data which you provide such as your name, address or telephone number, to any outside parties except with your permission or when we believe the law requires. However, we may record and share aggregated information with our partners. While we make all efforts to protect your privacy when negotiating our partnerships, we are not responsible for their use of your personal data. To that end, we encourage you to read the privacy statements of our partners, or request them directly from our partners in the event that they are not readily available. If you remain concerned about information disclosure, please contact us via the feedback section of our site, or at the address listed below.

**

IP Addresses

**

PropertyNews.com may collect IP addresses or other numeric codes used to identify a computer to help diagnose problems with our servers and for system administration. PropertyNews.com shall only use these addresses for technical and tracking purposes.

**

Log Files

**

PropertyNews.com captures industry standard information solely for the purposes of analysis. Information contained in log files is intended for internal use only and will not be disclosed to third parties (including our partners). The aggregate logged information is not linked to any personally identifiable data.

**

Feedback

**

Please submit any feedback to PropertyNews.com. Any feedback submitted becomes the property of PropertyNews.com. We may use this feedback, such as success stories, for marketing purposes, or to contact you for further feedback on the site. We will seek your written or email approval should we want to use your personal success story for marketing purposes. Feedback is used primarily for internal purposes to aid us in improving the site.

**

Hosting

**

This site is hosted and managed for us by [Kainos Software Limited](http://www.kainos.com/), Kainos House, 4-6 Upper Crescent, Belfast BT7 1NT.

**

Enquiries

**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this Website, or your dealings with this site, you can contact us by e-mail at [info@propertynews.com](mailto:info@propertynews.com), or at the following address: PropertyNews, 1 Annagh Drive, Carn Industrial Estate, Portadown, Co. Armagh, BT63 5RH
